[
  {
    "id": "T2C01",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "When do FCC rules NOT apply to the operation of an amateur station?",
    "answers": [
      "When operating a RACES station",
      "When operating under special FEMA rules",
      "When operating under special ARES rules",
      "FCC rules always apply"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T2C02",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which of the following are typical duties of a Net Control Station?",
    "answers": [
      "Choose the regular net meeting time and frequency",
      "Ensure that all stations checking into the net are properly licensed for operation on the net frequency",
      "Call the net to order and direct communications between stations checking in",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T2C03",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What technique is used to ensure that voice messages containing unusual words are received correctly?",
    "answers": [
      "Send the words by voice and Morse code",
      "Speak very loudly into the microphone",
      "Spell the words using a standard phonetic alphabet",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T2C04",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What is RACES?",
    "answers": [
      "An emergency organization combining amateur radio and citizens band operators and frequencies",
      "An international radio experimentation society",
      "A radio contest held in a short period, sometimes called a “sprint”",
      "An FCC part 97 amateur radio service for civil defense communications during national emergencies"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T2C05",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What does the term “traffic” refer to in net operation?",
    "answers": [
      "Messages exchanged by net stations",
      "The number of stations checking in and out of a net",
      "Operation by mobile or portable stations",
      "Requests to activate the net by a served agency"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T2C06",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What is the Amateur Radio Emergency Service (ARES)?",
    "answers": [
      "A group of licensed amateurs who have voluntarily registered their qualifications and equipment for communications duty in the public service",
      "A group of licensed amateurs who are members of the military and who voluntarily agreed to provide message handling services in the case of an emergency",
      "A training program that provides licensing courses for those interested in obtaining an amateur license to use during emergencies",
      "A training program that certifies amateur operators for membership in the Radio Amateur Civil Emergency Service"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T2C07",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "Which of the following is standard practice when you participate in a net?",
    "answers": [
      "When first responding to the net control station, transmit your call sign, name, and address as in the FCC database",
      "Record the time of each of your transmissions",
      "Unless you are reporting an emergency, transmit only when directed by the net control station",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T2C08",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of good traffic handling?",
    "answers": [
      "Passing messages exactly as received",
      "Making decisions as to whether messages are worthy of relay or delivery",
      "Ensuring that any newsworthy messages are relayed to the news media",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T2C09",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "Are amateur station control operators ever permitted to operate outside the frequency privileges of their license class?",
    "answers": [
      "No",
      "Yes, but only when part of a FEMA emergency plan",
      "Yes, but only when part of a RACES emergency plan",
      "Yes, but only in situations involving the immediate safety of human life or protection of property"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T2C10",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What information is contained in the preamble of a formal traffic message?",
    "answers": [
      "The email address of the originating station",
      "The address of the intended recipient",
      "The telephone number of the addressee",
      "Information needed to track the message"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T2C11",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "What is meant by “check” in a radiogram header?",
    "answers": [
      "The number of words or word equivalents in the text portion of the message",
      "The call sign of the originating station",
      "A list of stations that have relayed the message",
      "A box on the message form that indicates that the message was received and/or relayed"
    ]
  }
]